A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accession 2017:050 FA1304
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Publications, 1
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 2003 - The Next Information Age: Reality TV the World Should Be Watching, Vol. 34, No. 3 (3 copies) (Box 51, Folder 659)
  - From Birth to Death and Bench to Clinic: The Hastings Center Bioethics Briefing Book for Journalists, Policymakers, and Campaigns, 2008-2009 (Box 51, Folder 660)
  - The Ford Foundation: The Formative Years, William Greenleaf, undated (Box 51, Folder 661-667, Box 52, Folder 668-670)
    An unpublished history of the Ford Foundation: Chapter I. A Broader Range, Chapter II. Charting A Course, Chapter III. Men and Issues, Chapter IV. A New Regime, Chapter V. Frontiers of Philanthropy: The United States, Chapter VI. Frontiers of Philanthropy: The World Arena, Chapter VII: Under Challenge, Chapter VIII. Foundation Titan, Chapter IX. The Pattern of Commitment, Chapter X. Transition
  - Patman and Foundations: Review and Assessment, Emerson F. Andrews, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - Ford Foundation Photo Library (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - Conference on Foundations, Dayton, Ohio, Sponsored by the Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1970 November 11-13 (Box 52, Folder 673)
  - Ford Foundation: Current Interests 1988 and 1989, 1988 January (Box 52, Folder 674)
  - The Rural Development and Community Foundations Initiative (2 copies), undated (Box 52, Folder 675)
  - Catalog of Publications Films and Videos (2 copies), 1993 July (Box 52, Folder 676, Box 110, Folder 1285)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency, Declaration on Civility and Inclusive Leadership: National Committee to Unite a Divided America, 2005 March (Box 52, Folder 677)
  - Ford Foundation Report Fall 2003 - In the Amazon: Tuning in to Women's Power, Vol. 34, No. 4 (2 copies) (Box 52, Folder 678)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 2003 - The Housing Puzzle, Vol. 34, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 52, Folder 679)
  - Program Reviews: South Africa and Namibia, 1993 March (Box 52, Folder 680)
  - Close to Home: Case Studies of Human Rights Work in the United States, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 681)
  - Arts Education for All: Lessons from the First Half of the Ford Foundation's National Arts Education Initiative, Gerri Spilka and Meg Long, the OMG Center for Collaborative Learning (2 copies), 2008 (Box 52, Folder 682)
  - International Collaboration in the Arts: A Report on the Ford Foundation Initiative, "Internationalizing New Work in the Performing Arts," Phase II, 1992-2002, Douglas Denatale, Ph.D. and Karen L. Ito, Ph. D. (Box 52, Folder 683)
    Edited by Mindy Levine, Report developed by New England Foundation for the Arts, Report edited and published by Arts International
  - Perspectives on India's Development in the 1990s, Seminar Papers, 1992 January 28-29 (Box 52, Folder 684)
    A Symposium: 28-29 January 1992, Nehru Memorial Museum Library, New Delhi
  - Improving Public Schools For All Children: Constituency-Building for Public School Reform, A Ford Foundation Initiative, undated (Box 52, Folder 685)
  - "Adult Leadership:" A Study of Subscribers and their Reactions to the Magazine, Survey Research Center, Institute for Social Research, University of Michigan, 1953 September (Box 53, Folder 686)
  - Leader's Digest No. 3: Variations on Persistent Themes, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1956 (Box 53, Folder 687)
    Selected Articles largely from Volumes III and IV of Adult Leadership
  - The Leader's Digest: The Best from Adult Leadership Volume No. 1, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1953 (Box 53, Folder 688)
  - The New American School for Adults, Louis K. Mather, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 689)
  - Architecture for Adult Education, Commission on Architecture: Adult Education Association, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 690)
    A graphic guide for those who are planning physical facilities for Adult Education
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 1, No. 1-11, 1952 May-1953 April (Box 53, Folder 691-701)
    No. 11. Evaluating Program and Performance, No. 10. Leading Discussion, No. 9. Initiating Social Action, No. 8. Spotlight on Member Roles, No. 7. Improving Large Meetings, No. 6. Getting and Keeping Members, No. 5. The Role in the Community, No. 4. Working Toward Goals, No. 3. Using Resources, No. 2. Spotlight on Leadership, No. 1. Program Planning (signed by Malcolm Knowles)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 2, No. 1-11, 1953 May-1954 April (Box 53, Folder 702-707, Box 54, Folder 708-712)
    No. 11. Workshop on...Social Science in Action, No. 10. Workshop on...Your Public Relations, No. 9. Workshop on: Personal Growth Through Group Experience, No. 8. Workshop on...Locals and Their Nationals, No. 7. Workshop on...The Dynamics of Work Groups, No. 6. Workshop on...Handling Controversial Issues, No. 5. Social Inventions for Learning, No. 4. Committees, Boards, and Officers, No. 3. Programing for World Affairs, No. 2. Leadership Training, No. 1. Conferences that Work
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 3, No. 1-10, 1954 May-1955 April (Box 54, Folder 713)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 4, No. 1-10, 1955 May-1956 April (Box 54, Folder 714)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 5, No. 1-10, 1956 May-1957 April (Box 54, Folder 715)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 6, No. 1-10, 1957 May-1958 April (Box 54, Folder 716)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 7, No. 1-10, 1958 May-1959 April (Box 54, Folder 717)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 8, No. 1-10, 1959 May-1960 April (Box 55, Folder 718)
  - Adult Education Association, Adult Leadership Magazine - Volume 9, No. 1-10, 1960 May-1961 April (Box 55, Folder 719)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring/Summer 1999 - Faith Matters: A Ministry for the Mean Streets, Vol. 30, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 720, Box 113, Folder 1316)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer/Fall 1997 - Changing the Faces at the Front of the Class, Vol. 28, No. 3 (Box 55, Folder 721)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 1996 - Special Report: South Africa and the Philippines Tackle Land Reform, Vol. 27, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 722, Box 113, Folder 1325)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer/Fall 1995 - Special Report: America's Unfinished Agenda: Jobs, Housing, Communities, Vol. 26, No. 3 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 723)
  - Current Interests of the Ford Foundation 1992 and 1993 (2 copies), 1992 May (Box 55, Folder 724, Box 110, Folder 1295)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer 1992 - From Brazil: Confronting Racial Inequities, Curbing Abuse of Women, Understanding the Earth Summit, Vol. 23, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 725, Box 113, Folder 1313)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 1997 - Volume 28, No. 1 (Box 55, Folder 726)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 2000 - An Honored Indian Nation Welcomes the Wolf, Volume 31, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 727, Box 113, Folder 1323)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 1996 - Looking Out for Families: Local Groups Lead the Way, Vol. 27, No. 2 (Box 55, Folder 728)
  - Ford Foundation Report Fall 1999 - Risking the Future of Our Cities: Uneven, Runaway Growth Is Leaving Many Communities Behind, Is There Another Way?, Volume 30, No. 3 (2 copies) (Box 55, Folder 729, Box 113, Folder 1317)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring/Summer 1998 - Can Inner-City Schools Provide a Path to Success?: Houston's Project GRAD Has Some Answers, Vol. 39, No. 2 (Box 55, Folder 730)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 2000 - A Special Issue on Women: Now It's a Global Movement, Vol. 31, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 56, Folder 731, Box 113, Folder 1324)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer/Fall 1996 - Making the Grade: Reforming America's Schools, Vol. 27, No. 3 (2 copies) (Box 56, Folder 732)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 1992 - Crossroads of Theatre: Coming of Age, Vol. 23, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 56, Folder 733, Box 113, Folder 1314)
  - Ford Foundation Letter Spring/Summer 1991 - Vol. 22, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 56, Folder 734, Box 113, Folder 1315)
  - Ford Foundation Letter Fall 1991 - Vol. 22, No. 2 (Box 56, Folder 735)
  - Ford Foundation Letter Winter 1991 - Vol. 22, No. 3 (Box 56, Folder 736)
  - Law: Ford Foundation Grantees and the Pursuit of Justice (2 copies), 2000 February (Box 56, Folder 737, Box 110, Folder 1286)
  - Investing for Social Gain: Reflections on Two Decades of Program-Related Investments, A Ford Foundation Report, 1991 December (Box 56, Folder 738)
    Includes correspondence and supplementary information in addition to the publication
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report 1998 - President's Message, 1999 June (Box 56, Folder 739)
  - Collaborations that Count: Working for Democracy in Devolutionary Times (2 copies), 2000 July (Box 56, Folder 740, Box 110, Folder 1289)
  - Updates 1992: Innovations in State and Local Government, 1986 to 1991 (Box 56, Folder 741)
  - Commercial Lending Disclosure and Economic Development: A Plan for Action, Josh Hoyt, Woodstock Institute, Chicago, Illinois, 1988 April (Box 56, Folder 742)
  - Experiences in Building Cross-Field Partnerships for Sexuality and Reproductive Health (2 copies), 2001 January (Box 56, Folder 743)
  - Reproductive Health: A Strategy for the 1990s, A Program Paper of the Ford Foundation, 1991 June (Box 56, Folder 744)
  - A Fundação Ford no Brasil, The Ford Foundation in Brazil, 1998/1999 (Box 56, Folder 745)
  - Three Essays: Black Studies in the United States, Robert L. Harris, Jr., Darlene Clark Hine, and Nellie McKay, 1990 June (Box 57, Folder 746)
  - Ford Foundation Office of Communications Style Guide, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 747)
  - Ford Foundation Office of Communications Style Guide, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 747)
  - Gender Bias in Testing: Current Debates, Future Priorities, 1991 May (Box 57, Folder 748)
    Ford Foundation Women's Program Forum, A public policy dialogue
  - Forty Years: A Learning Curve, The Ford Foundation Programs in India, 1952-1992, Eugene S. Staples (2 copies) (Box 57, Folder 749)
  - Building Bridges: Community Development Corporations and the World of Employment Training, Bennett Harrison, Marcus Weiss, and Jon Gant, A Report to the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1995 January (Box 57, Folder 750)
  - Civil Rights, Social Justice, and Black America, A Working Paper from the Ford Foundation, 1984 January (Box 57, Folder 751)
    A review of past and current Ford Foundation efforts to promote racial justice for black Americans in employment, education, housing, political participation, and other areas
  - Affordable Housing: The Years Ahead, A Program Paper of the Ford Foundation, 1989 August (Box 57, Folder 752)
  - Violence Against Women: Addressing a Global Problem, Ford Foundation Women's Program Forum, 1992 March (Box 57, Folder 753)
  - The Finances of the Performing Arts, Volume 1: A Survey of 166 Professional Nonprofit Resident Theaters, Operas, Symphonies, Ballets, and Modern Dance Companies, A Ford Foundation Report (2 copies), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 754, Box 111, Folder 1298)
  - Energy: The Next Twenty Years, A Report Sponsored by the Ford Foundation, Administered by Resources for the Future, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 755)
  - Reproduction and Human Welfare: A Challenge to Research, A Review of the Reproductive Sciences and Contraceptive Development, Roy O. Greep, Marjorie A. Koblinsky, and Frederick S. Jaffe, Sponsored by the Ford Foundation, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 756-757, Box 84, Folder 1000, Box 110, Folder 1294)
    Folder 756 contains a reprint from BioScience and a letter of introduction from McGeorge Bundy; Folder 757 contains the published work; Box 84 and Box 110 contain two more copies of the published work
  - Grant-Talk Video Notes, Junko Chano (2 copies), 2000 (Box 58, Folder 758)
    Includes Mozambique Sustainable Wilderness Development Initiative, Ken Wilson; Community Based Fisheries Management Initiative, Doris Capistrano, and Strengthening Fragile Families Initiative, Ron Mincy
  - Innovating America, Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation and the John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, Fred Jordan, 1990 July (Box 58, Folder 759)
  - Innovations in American Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1986-1996, Tenth Anniversary (2 copies), 1996 December (Box 58, Folder 760, Box 110, Folder 1290)
  - Alliance: Building Resources for the Community Worldwide, Vol. 6, No. 2, Charities Aid Foundation (CAF), 2001 June (Box 58, Folder 761)
  - Quality Preschool Programs: A Long-Term Social Investment, David P. Weikart, Occasional Paper 5, Ford Foundation Project on Social Welfare and the American Future, 1989 June (Box 58, Folder 762)
  - The Ford Foundation in Eastern and Southern Africa, 2001-2005 (Box 58, Folder 763)
  - The United Nations in Its Second Half-Century: The Report of the Independent Working Group on the Future of the United Nations, undated (Box 58, Folder 764)
  - Refugees and Migrants: Problems and Program Responses, A Working Paper from the Ford Foundation, 1983 August (Box 58, Folder 765)
    A look at the causes and consequences of today's major international population flows, and at the Ford Foundation's new programs to address the problems of refugees and migrants in the United States and elsewhere in the world
  - Renewing the United Nations System, Erskine Childers with Brian Urquhart, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 766)
  - Nuclear Power Issues and Choices: Overview, Excerpt from the Report of the Nuclear Energy Policy Study Group, Sponsored by the Ford Foundation, Administered by the MITRE Corporation, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 767)
  - Afro-American Studies, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Nathan Huggins, 1985 July (Box 58, Folder 768)
  - In Quest of Knowledge: A Historical Perspective on Adult Education, C. Hartley Grattan, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 769)
  - Learning Comes of Age, John Walker Powell, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 770)
    A survey and interpretation of the aims, instruments, clientele, and leadership of Adult Education - as it is now and as it can be in the future.
  - Civil Defense for Adult Americans: What You, Your Friends, Your Neighbors, and Your Community Can Do for Civil Defense, Adult Education Monograph No. 3, 2001-2007 (Box 59, Folder 771)
  - A Complete Transcript of the Lafayette Conference of the Professors of Adult Education, Lafayette, Indiana, 1958 August (Box 59, Folder 772)
  - Professors of Adult Education 1960 Conference Proceedings: A Complete Transcript of the East Lansing Conference of the Professors of Adult Education, East Lansing, Michigan, 1960 April 11-13 (Box 59, Folder 773)
  - A Report on the Ann Arbor Conference of the Professors of Adult Education, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1957 October (Box 59, Folder 774)
    Note from original folder: #572-AEA, Conference of Professors of Adult Education, April 1957, Archives, FAE
  - Seeking Common Ground in Adult Education, Robertson Sillars, Adult Education Monographs, No. 4, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 775)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #1: How to Lead Discussions, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1955 (Box 60, Folder 776)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #2: Planning Better Programs, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 777)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #4: Understanding How Groups Work, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1955 (Box 60, Folder 778)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #5: How to Teach Adults, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1955 (Box 60, Folder 779)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #6: How to Use Role Playing and Other Tools for Learning, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1955 (Box 60, Folder 780)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #7: Supervision and Consultation, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1956 (Box 60, Folder 781)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #8: Training Group Leaders, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1956 (Box 60, Folder 782)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #9: Conducting Workshops and Institutes, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1956 (Box 60, Folder 783)
  - Leadership Pamphlet #10: Working With Volunteers, Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1956 (Box 60, Folder 784)
  - Financing Adult Education: In America's Public Schools and Community Councils, Edward B. Olds, National Commission on Adult Education Finance, undated (Box 60, Folder 785)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IV, No. 5, 1954 May (Box 60, Folder 786)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IV, No. 4, 1954 March (Box 60, Folder 787)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IV, No. 3, 1954 February (Box 60, Folder 788)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IV, No. 1, 1953 November (Box 60, Folder 789)
  - Adult Education, Vol. III, No. 5, 1953 May (Box 60, Folder 790)
  - Adult Education, Vol. III, No. 4 - Adult Education and Mass Communications, Robert B. Hudson, Issue Editor, 1953 March (Box 60, Folder 791)
  - Adult Education, Vol. III, No. 1, 1952 November (Box 60, Folder 792)
  - Adult Education, Vol. II, No. 6 - Some Trends in Adult Education, A Symposium, 1952 September (Box 60, Folder 793)
  - Adult Education, Vol. II, No. 2, 1951 December (Box 60, Folder 794)
  - Adult Education, Vol. I, No. 6 - "Working Together for Better Communities," First National Conference, Adult Education Association of the United States of America, 1951 August (Box 60, Folder 795)
  - Adult Education, Vol. I, No. 5 - Adult Education Association of the United States of America, Founded May 14, 1951, 1951 June (Box 60, Folder 796)
  - Adult Education, Have You Heard About Plans for the New Association?, Founding Assembly, Columbus, Ohio, 1951 May (Box 60, Folder 797)
  - Adult Education, Vol. I, No. 3, 1951 February (Box 60, Folder 798)
  - Adult Education. Vol. X, No. 3, Spring 1960 (Box 60, Folder 799)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VII, No. 4, Summer 1957 (Box 60, Folder 800)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VIII, No. 3, Spring 1958 (Box 60, Folder 801)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VIII, No. 2, Winter 1958 (Box 61, Folder 802)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VIII, No. 1, Autumn 1957 (Box 61, Folder 803)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VII, No. 2, Winter 1957 (Box 61, Folder 804)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VI, No. 3, Spring 1956 (Box 61, Folder 805)
  - Adult Education, Vol. V, No. 4, Summer 1955 (Box 61, Folder 806)
  - Adult Education, Vol. V, No. 3, Spring 1955 (Box 61, Folder 807)
  - Adult Education, Vol. V, No. 2, Winter 1955 (Box 61, Folder 808)
  - Adult Education, Vol. V, No. 1, Autumn 1954 (Box 61, Folder 809)
  - Adult Education, Vol. XI, No. 2, Winter 1961 (Box 61, Folder 810)
  - Adult Education, Vol. XI, No. 1, Autumn 1960 (Box 61, Folder 811)
  - Adult Education, Vol. X, No. 2, Winter 1960 (Box 61, Folder 812)
  - Adult Education, Vol. X, No. 1, Autumn 1959 (Box 61, Folder 813)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IX, No. 4, Summer 1959 (Box 61, Folder 814)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IX, No. 3, Spring 1959 (Box 61, Folder 815)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IX, No. 2, Winter 1959 (Box 61, Folder 816)
  - Adult Education, Vol. IX, No. 1, Autumn 1958 (Box 61, Folder 817)
  - Adult Education, Vol. VIII, No. 4, Summer 1958 (Box 61, Folder 818)
  - Ford Reports, Number One 2007 - The Ford Foundation Magazine of Ideas and Action - Opening Doors to the Economic Mainstream (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 819)
  - Ford Reports, Number Two 2007 - The Ford Foundation Magazine of Ideas and Action - The Public Square in a Digital Age (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 820)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 2005 - Texas New-Step: In Dallas, Arts Education Brings the Three R's To Life, Vol. 36, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 821)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring/Summer 2005 - The New Global City: Bigger, Richer, Poorer, Vol. 36, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 822)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 2004 - L.A. Rising, Vol. 35, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 823)
  - Ford Foundation Report Fall 2004 - Capital Ideas: New Ways to Bring Millions of Americans into the Economic Mainstream, Vol. 35, No. 4 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 824)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer 2004 - When Science Listens to Women, Vol. 35, No. 3 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 825)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 2004 - Facing AIDS: Can Nigeria's Youth Set a New Course for Africa?, Vol. 35, No. 2 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 826)
  - Ford Foundation Report Summer 2003 - Barely Making It: The Changing Workplace, New Help for Working Families, Vol. 34, No. 3 (Box 62, Folder 827)
  - Ford Foundation Report Winter 2002 - Islam and Human Rights, Vol. 33, No. 1 (2 copies) (Box 62, Folder 828)
  - Ford Foundation Report Spring 2002 - Culture and Nature in Yunnan, Vol. 33, No. 2 (Box 62, Folder 829)
  - America at the Polls 1996, Regina Dougherty, Everett C. Ladd, David Wilber, and Lynn Zayachkiwsky, The Roper Center for Public Opinion Research, University of Connecticut, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 830)
  - Writing Reform: A Guide to Drafting State & Local Campaign Finance Laws, Deborah Goldberg, Editor, Brennan Center for Justice at NYU School of Law, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 831)
  - Money and Politics: A Regional Study on Campaign Finance Laws in the West, Samantha Sanchez and Ed Bender, Western States Center, undated (Box 62, Folder 832)
    The Money in Western Politics Project - Oregon, Washington, Idaho, Montana, Wyoming, Utah, Nevada, Alaska
  - The Price of Democracy: The High & Hidden Costs of Politics in the West, Samantha Sanchez and Ed Bender, Western States Center, undated (Box 62, Folder 833)
    The Money in Western Politics Project - Oregon, Washington, Idaho, Montana, Wyoming, Utah, Nevada, and Alaska
  - The Nonprofit Quarterly - Vol. VI, No. 4, Winter 1999 - Building Capacity: A Co-Creation Approach (Box 63, Folder 834)
  - The Nonprofit Quarterly - Vol. 7, Issue 1 - Technology: Humanware Matters Most!, 2000 August (Box 63, Folder 835)
  - The Nonprofit Quarterly - Vol. 7, Issue 2 - Advocacy: Oh Yes You Can...And Should!, 2000 December (Box 63, Folder 836)
  - Asian American Voting Rights and Representation: A Perspective from the Northeast, Glenn D. Magpantay, Fordham Urban Law Journal, Vol. XXVIII, No. 3, 2001 February (Box 63, Folder 837)
  - Report on the Discrimination of Lesbians, Gay Men and Bisexuals in Hungary, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 838)
  - Exemplary Grantmaking Practices Manual, Ellen Furnari, Carol Mollner, Teresa Odendahl, and Aileen Shaw, National Network of Grantmakers, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 839)
  - America's Modern Poll Tax: How Structural Disenfranchisement Erodes Democracy, Steven Donziger, Advancement Project, 2001 November 7 (Box 63, Folder 840)
  - Lessons From The Street: Capacity Building and Replication, The Milton S. Eisenhower Foundation Twentieth Anniversary Series, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 841)
  - 200,000 in 2000: New Americans Pledging to Strengthen Democracy and New York, The New York Immigration Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 842)
  - Voter's Self-Defense Manual, 2000 Edition, Project Vote Smart, undated (Box 63, Folder 843)
  - The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science: The Media and Politics, Kathleen Hall Jamieson, 1996 July (Box 63, Folder 844)
  - Building a Better Democracy: Reflections on Money, Politics, and Free Speech, Burt Neuborne, Brennan Center for Justice at NYU School of Law, undated (Box 63, Folder 845)
  - Preventing Dropouts Through School-Community Collaboration, Education Resources Group, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 846)
  - Homeownership Built to Last: Balancing Access, Affordability, and Risk After the Housing Crisis, Eric S. Belsky, Christopher E. Herbert, and Jennifer H. Molinsky, Joint Center for Housing Studies, 2014 (Box 64, Folder 847)